{
  "name": "data/templates/CrazyMorningMale.txt",
  "answers": [
    {"answer": "name2"},
    {"answer": "band"},
    {"answer": "product"},
    {"answer": "company2"},
    {"answer": "bf gdfgrgrw"},
    {"answer": "gr dgrg"},
    {"answer": "eere"},
    {"answer": "567"},
    {"answer": "rtrt"}
  ],
  "prompts": [
    {"prompt": "Choose a food"},
    {"prompt": "Choose an animal"},
    {"prompt": "Now the animal's name"},
    {"prompt": "Choose a country"},
    {"prompt": "And another country"},
    {"prompt": "Name a fast person"},
    {"prompt": "Name a vehicle"},
    {"prompt": "Name a kind of building"},
    {"prompt": "Choose a number"},
    {"prompt": "Name a room (e.g. attic, living room)"},
    {"prompt": "Choose an emotion"},
    {"prompt": "Name a component of the product above"},
    {"prompt": "Name a candy"},
    {"prompt": "Name an adjective"},
    {"prompt": "And another adjective"},
    {"prompt": "Choose a bodypart"}
  ]
}